Hello Hello Friends Welcome to my channel
Friends today we are going to talk about a company
which is merging with another company a
total amount commission a very big merger
between two companies
this is one in if you have
seen the news design then a little bit you are
following Overtime Up channel etc then
you should see that this is a bit of a season going on right now
where a position Maurya swap all
this is happening a lot type Shishu
my online public of a lot and there is a lot of such
where fund collection is happening so these
companies are trying to gain more
market share than the market so that they can increase their profit
or they should schedule their own here
that company
is present with another company to increase it so a lot of Man Singh
and Life should be present so continuing the same, there is
just one merger happening in a lot
you are seeing that it is not seen in your home
so I will read a little news and tell you
what is the balance of the company which is specific to the city after the end of March, should you
take the said or not
We will talk about that in this video. So friends, the scenario that I am
talking about here is basically
Bhartiya Axa, which you know is the
Bhartiya Insurance Group, its
calibrated insurance company
and ICICI Lombard, which are two companies. We have to
talk about the merger of both the companies. Both the companies are going to be
merged. They are informed
and after this merger,
what is the business of the company, what is the status of the company, so
about that, the first
important thing is
who is forced with whom, so Bhartiya Axa is
basically going to end,
that friend is getting killed
with ICICI Lombard, so sample two-three
things the company has done here, so first of all it was
told that Bharti Axa General policy
holders will get the same or similar at the
time of the novel. This thing is
favorite to some that now we can say that
any two companies can have fun and if the first
company ends and the dream of the second one will go, then
what about the existing policy holders.
How will their sports lovers
fare, their policy will not be affected by cancer. So
here a PIN company has told that
even after March, there is a renewal
time, so in such countries, whatever finger type
polythene is said, the company should do it for
its meeting customers, this will
not make any difference to the already existing customers because their
brand is not changing, such
number and Indian General Insurance has not merged into some other countries, it is the
third
largest general insurance company, so
basically you should understand why this is being done, that is the only
reason so that they can
make their president more powerful in the market because it is
difficult to try in the market alone, you can
take any company, now since
Reliance Jio has come, to complete that balance,
Vodafone will match with Idea,
now you have been
present in Airtel for a long time
with anyone, so to remain in competition,
you will either have to do this point or
you will have to match a sponge culture, it is
not possible if you have money  There is
no capital, Reliance which is such a big
company, which has the right to peer baby in the biggest company of India, is
among the top companies, it is
also telling other foreign investors
that you should take my stand and
invest money in my company so that it can do
more than just capital and vital, so
capital is needed, so every
company has captained to a pan, due to which you
can see here, both these companies are going to be the
third largest
general insurance company of the country, that is,
school from Insurance Regulatory and
Development Authority and Competition Commission of
India, subscribe, do not subscribe,
pimples pacer getting up at this point of
time, both are different, if we talk percentage wise, then
you can see here Bharti
Enterprises,
both together are Indian companies,
subscribe The Channel And subscribe The
Amazing company said that to keep the
company always with each other,
subscribe definitely lot
quarter things told that what they should do and what they should
not do, so the most important
factors are told here, I
said that in the first point I told that
policy  Whoever the holder is, you will
get Shimla time now, there will be no problem with the existing ones,
but all this is
normal, a customer friends and point to give
positive,
what changes are happening with them, but the most important
thing to pay attention to here is that the
news that you get, both are
very good and big, both subscribe and
you will discuss a little bit about the company here, so to
discuss it, I told you a sample here,
Atif Aslam Butt, this
company which is the parent company with which
this margin is happening,
click a little bit about this company today, we
will see that it has a high level rally for its internship, as of
today's date, this typing,
it is trading in the market, is it there or
not, when the price can go high, can it go low,
now it has to fold and
what can be its features, we will
discuss about that, so I have told you about other things about it,
what is the news or the
match of Indian instruments, now let us
move ahead and see a little bit about the fundamental
position of the company  So friends, if
you have seen my first video, then you
know how I do fundamental rights in this. If I do
not find it here,
this is the best parameter which I use to
judge any company.
First of all, if we
talk about the market cap of any company, it should be more than thousand crores.
If you
call it a good company, if you think of it for long term investment, you
can see the clear time here.
Market capital is
more than 130 Divya 10.5 percent here at
this point to 8 9 tags page 10 48. So
as I told you that there is a
big company like Reliance, because it is a little bit too
much, then it should be
on the subscribe button. This 2% 10
in 2008 should be subscribed. And finally,
according to Bigg Boss Hansel growth rate, that company
sometimes this rock is between 510 Prasanna.
Due to the demand, the company is
doing optimal business. The sales percentage here
is up to 26.41 percent to judge friends, if
we use this totka meter.  If we reduce it from then I have to
decide the fixed points here and reduce
them to lower quantity percent, then the
fundamentals and basic parameters of a company
which I hope to achieve at
60%, then I can assume
that the company is not worth ignoring, the
company seems good to me, now at this point
time also a news has come that it is going to be very
big, so I think
definitely subscribe interview, it
looks very bad, so from here 60 percent and
here in this because subscribe, then
subscribe, subscribe, all of
you friends, this is a simple thing, so you know,
friends, read the company, but now we
definitely have to know what should be the curve of the company, the
company is
doing business in the market today, the valuation of the company, according to which the
picture collected in the market today,
what is the price at which the company closed, it can be disrupted, so
for research I have shown here, if
you have not seen the old videos of the channel, then
you should do it right now,
on the playlist  Take it and send the interest to the
next subject.
I have seen the intrinsic value of all these companies in tempered glass. If you
watch the video in it,
you will be able to do your own analysis. It is
not necessary that every time it will depend on you that I will
upload a new video. Now if you
feel that this is the middle method, then you
can do your own research on this
etc., then you can ask me by commenting on this
channel. If you want to watch old videos,
when can you go and playlist me in the
valley, then in
that session,
journalism in Brahma Cup is the maximum. For that,
we use three parameters, first meter
running share, second growth and this pond. These
three will give you basic information on any company's
control comment anywhere,
if we
talk about earnings per share, this is 28.1. If
we talk about group, this point is the
analysis, accordingly, if we take the body on today's
date, this is 5.45, then intensive, this is my
calibration, like 1470 Lokayukta.  14
My intrinsic value of this company is coming out to be ₹70, which should be
its first option.
This uniform has satisfactory
fundamental data, but today's
project price has been closed in the company,
it is profitable. If we look at this program,
a company has made a profit. So from here if we
look at the intrinsic value, at least here
we friends, ₹10 is amazing. It seems
special. Almost 20%
today in the office price, it is trading at
least 10% from there.
I think that now a
possible key is formed in this. If its record exam
schedule commission news comes in the market, then
you can see on one side, there is a little bulb
price, you can subscribe to this
war because
I thought that if you liked the video, I
thought that you liked the way I did it, then
you can use it. If
you think that you liked the video, then
definitely tell me and if you want to know about this company, then I should
appoint the chairman of the company and do it, so right now, watch the
video as much as possible.
Share it more with your friends and tips.
If you like the content, then the most important
thing is to subscribe to the channel because
your subscription is what increases my ability to make videos. My
video Love
and After Subset Jasmine is also very important for you
and the most important thing is that you
must write in the comment section and tell me
what you liked in the video and what
you did not like, what can be
improved more, on which topic do
you want more videos, that is very important for me
so that I can make the best of the best videos for you. Stay tuned for the
video.
Thank you very much and
very soon I will bring some new and good
hourly video which is beneficial for you. So
thank you so much for making the video.
Thank you very much to all of you. Have a nice day.